Zach Harmon

zachha@gmail.com | (919) 357-7962 | Holly Springs, NC

https://www.zachha.com https://github.com/zachha https://www.linkedin.com/in/zach

SUMMARY

Experienced researcher and tech-enthusiast who has a passion for learning. Recently graduated with a B.S. in Computer Science. Experience with full stack web development tools including: Node.js, Express, JavaScript, React.js, GIT, Github, MongoDB, MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, APIs, JSON, REST, AJAX, the command line, and computer science fundamentals. Small application experience using Javascript and to a lesser extent, Python, Java, and Lua. Has a strong knowledge base in science and the medical field.

APPLICATIONS BUILT

Netflix Recommender

A full-stack web application created using node.js and express that utilizes a mongoDB database. The application allows users to search for a movie/tv show in the Netflix library and get a list of recommended titles based off of the selected title. The application implements a euclidean distance algorithm to sort movies by similarity and genre and then gives the user a list of recommended titles to watch.

Sole Developer https://github.com/zachha/Netflix-Recommender https://show-recommender.herokuapp.com/

Package Deliveries

A Python application created using Object Oriented Programming that simulates two delivery trucks attempting to deliver packages as quickly and accurately as they can. The application utilizes Djikstra's Shortest Path algorithm with a Priority Queue to calculate the fastest route to deliver the packages.

Sole Developer https://github.com/zachha/Package-Deliveries

Node Storefronts

A Node.js CLI application created with a mysql database to emulate a small store that sells items. Allows a user to login as a buyer, a manager, or a supervisor with different permissions and related store operations for each role.

Sole Developer https://github.com/zachha/node-storefronts

PREVIOUS EXPERIENCE

Clinical Cancer Research (Durham, NC)

• **Senior Clinical Research Specialist** - GYN/Oncology, Duke University Hospital, NC **(2015-2017)** Worked with physicians and patients to fulfill cancer clinical trials and to collect/use medical data

Volunteering

•	All Things Open Volunteer - Tech Volunteer in Raleigh, NC	(2018-2023)
•	EMT-B Volunteer – Duke University Hospital ER/Cary EMT	(2017)
•	Pediatric/Emergency Department Volunteer – UNC Hospital, Chapel Hill, NC	(2013-2014)
•	Red Cross Disaster Action Team (DAT) Member – North Carolina	(2013-2016)

PUBLICATIONS

Davidson BA, E Jessie, Abbott S, Harmon Z, et al. Prospective Evaluation of Lymph Node Processing at Staging Surgery for High-grade Endometrial Cancer. *Int J Gynecol Pathol*. 2018;37(3):252-255.

EDUCATION

Western Governors University - North Carolina

2019-2022, Obtained a B.S. in Computer Science

University of North Carolina at Wilmington

2009-2012, Obtained a B.A. in Film Studies